welectronics.com 2018-12-26

# Overseas Electronics www.welectronics.com Privacy Policy

Privacy policy:

We take your privacy very seriously. This privacy policy lets you know what information we collect, share, and your choices regarding sharing of your information. This policy applies to Overseas Electronics Inc., dba-Welectronics.com and other places where we may collect personal information. If you have any questions or concerns you may email us at [ labbek@aol.com](mailto:labbek@aol.com) (subject: Privacy) further you may mail us at:

Overseas Electronics Inc. dba/ Welectronics.com

2457 W. Devon Ave

Chicago, IL 60659-1914

Information We Collect: 

  * Any information you give us, such as during transactions, customer service, surveys, and online registrations.
  * Any information from other sources, such as consumer reporting agencies, and
  * Any information automatically collected when you visit our websites, such as via cookies, and in stores, e.g. via video cameras.

How we use that information:

  * Overseas Electronics Inc. does not sell or rent any of your private information to third parties. 
  * Overseas Electronics Inc. uses the information to improve functions such as customer service, logistics, and internal operations etc. 
  * Overseas Electronics Inc. may share certain personal information with third parties such as financial institutions, credit card companies, and if a need arises to protect and support Overseas Electronics Inc. and its affiliates. 

Consumer Opt Out:

  * Overseas Electronics Inc. does communicate and market certain products via email or mail, but the option is left to the consumer if they would like to receive such promotions. 
  * Overseas Electronics Inc. uses an opt-out standard for such communications and will not further communicate if the consumer opts-out of such communication. 

Legal Necessities:

We may share your information in other special circumstances. These include situations when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or that the sharing is necessary to protect the safety, property, or other rights of Overseas Electronics Inc., our customers, our associates, or any other person. Examples include protecting the health or safety of customers, or addressing crimes committed on Overseas Electronics Inc. property. Data from in-store security cameras may also be provided to law enforcement upon written request.

Security: 

We use industry standard security 128 bit encrypted SSL servers. Welectronics.com. takes precautions to protect its customers' information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

When our registration/order form asks you to enter sensitive information (such as your credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software currently available in the industry - SSL. Welectronics.com uses the most advanced form of SSL software available: 128-bit encryption by Cart32™. To learn more about SSL, follow this link [ www.cart32.com](http://www.cart32.com/).

Welectronics.com is certified by McAfee™  Security. The McAfee SECURE™ Trustmark only appears when the website has passed McAfee’s intensive, daily security scan. McAfee test for possible personal information access, links to dangerous sites, phishing, and other online dangers.

Welectronics.com accepts Google™  Checkout for payments on purchases. To access Google Checkout’s privacy policy please go to:  <https://checkout.google.com/files/privacy.html>

Welectronics.com accepts Paypal™   for payments on purchases. To access Paypal’s Privacy Policy please go to: [ https://cms.paypal.com/cgi-bin/marketingweb?cmd=_render-content&content_ID=ua/Privacy_full&locale.x=en_US](https://cms.paypal.com/cgi-bin/marketingweb?cmd=_render-content&content_ID=ua/Privacy_full&locale.x=en_US) 

Overseas Electronics Chicago and its Employees will never ask for a money gram or western union money transfer . we are not listed on alibaba or sell on Aliexpress . Give us a call or email us as we are available during our Business hours for any questions or Concerns.

Questions:

Please email us if you have any questions at [ Labbek@aol.com](mailto:Labbek@aol.com) (Subject: Privacy), or you may Mail in your request at:

Overseas Electronics Inc. dba/ Welectronics.com

2457 W. Devon Ave

Chicago, IL 60659-1914

“Wholesale to Public”

We are a wholesale distributor to business and the public. We buy wholesale directly from the manufacturers at incredible discounts. We then break up case lots to distribute wholesale to the public. Our no minimum order policy allows individuals to purchase thousands of products at incredibly low price. 

We can sell wholesale to anyone. With a no minimum order policy as well as a wholesale to the public policy you do not have to spend a lot of money to save a lot of money. We do offer large discounts for bulk purchasers.

Welectronics.com is dedicated to making wholesale buying available to everyone in the world. We will continue to keep our doors open to the public and allow anyone to purchase our quality products at affordable prices.
